const e={sections:[{header:{text:"Choose the correct option"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"The keys ____ on the table.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"were left",2:"was left",3:"are left",4:"leaves"}},{type:"test",question:"The concert ____ at the stadium.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was being held",2:"held",3:"was holding",4:"holds"}},{type:"test",question:"This song ____ by many people.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"is liked",2:"likes",3:"was liked",4:"liked"}},{type:"test",question:"The documents ____ in the office.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"were stored",2:"stores",3:"stored",4:"are storing"}},{type:"test",question:"The meeting ____ for 3 PM.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was scheduled",2:"is scheduled",3:"schedules",4:"scheduling"}},{type:"test",question:"The problem ____ yesterday.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was solved",2:"was solving",3:"solves",4:"solving"}},{type:"test",question:"The news ____ by everyone.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"had been heard",2:"heard",3:"was hearing",4:"is being heard"}},{type:"test",question:"The message ____ to the manager.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was given",2:"gives",3:"giving",4:"gave"}},{type:"test",question:"The application ____ by the IT department.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was developed",2:"is developing",3:"developed",4:"develops"}},{type:"test",question:"The mistake ____ by him.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was corrected",2:"corrected",3:"is correcting",4:"corrects"}}]},{header:{text:"Choose the correct verb form Active or Passive:"},exercises:[{type:"select",lines:[[{text:"The Missing Laptop."}],[{text:"Yesterday, Sarah's laptop"},{placeholder:"choose",rightAnswerId:"a",answers:{a:"was stolen",b:"stole",c:"has stolen",d:"stealing"}},{text:"from her office."},{text:"She"},{placeholder:"choose",rightAnswerId:"a",answers:{a:"left",b:"was left",c:"leaves",d:"leaving"}},{text:"her office door unlocked when she"},{placeholder:"choose",rightAnswerId:"c",answers:{a:"was going",b:"goes",c:"went",d:"has gone"}},{text:"out to lunch."},{text:"When she"},{placeholder:"choose",rightAnswerId:"a",answers:{a:"was returned",b:"is returning",c:"returned",d:"returns"}},{text:"to the office, her laptop"},{placeholder:"choose",rightAnswerId:"b",answers:{a:"has been stolen",b:"had been stolen",c:"steals",d:"is stolen"}},{text:"to check the security cameras."}],[{text:"The security cameras"},{placeholder:"choose",rightAnswerId:"a",answers:{a:"were called",b:"calls",c:"have called",d:"called"}},{text:"the office entrance, and they"},{placeholder:"choose",rightAnswerId:"c",answers:{a:"is recording",b:"recorded",c:"records",d:"was recording"}},{text:"that a man in a hat and sunglasses"},{placeholder:"choose",rightAnswerId:"a",answers:{a:"identified",b:"identifies",c:"was identified",d:"identifying"}},{text:"the laptop."},{text:"The laptop"},{placeholder:"choose",rightAnswerId:"a",answers:{a:"took",b:"was taking",c:"takes",d:"take"}},{text:"from the office."}]]}]},{header:{text:"Choose the variant that can't be used in the sentences"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"The keys ____ on the table.",rightAnswerIds:["c"],answers:{a:"has been left",b:"are left",c:"leaves",d:"were left"}},{type:"test",question:"The concert ____ at the stadium.",rightAnswerIds:["b"],answers:{a:"is held",b:"is holding",c:"was held",d:"has been held"}},{type:"test",question:"This song ____ by many people.",rightAnswerIds:["b"],answers:{a:"is liked",b:"likes",c:"was liked",d:"had been liked"}},{type:"test",question:"The documents ____ in the office.",rightAnswerIds:["c"],answers:{a:"are stored",b:"were stored",c:"are storing",d:"were being stored"}},{type:"test",question:"The meeting ____ for 3 PM.",rightAnswerIds:["b"],answers:{a:"is scheduled",b:"schedules",c:"was scheduled",d:"will be scheduled"}},{type:"test",question:"The problem ____ by them.",rightAnswerIds:["a"],answers:{a:"was solving",b:"was solved",c:"will be solved",d:"has been solved"}},{type:"test",question:"The news ____ by everyone.",rightAnswerIds:["b"],answers:{a:"was heard",b:"was hearing",c:"is heard",d:"will be heard"}},{type:"test",question:"The message ____ to the manager.",rightAnswerIds:["b"],answers:{a:"was given",b:"gives",c:"had been given",d:"will be given"}},{type:"test",question:"The application ____ by the IT department.",rightAnswerIds:["a"],answers:{a:"is developing",b:"is developed",c:"was developed",d:"has been developed"}},{type:"test",question:"The mistakes ____ by him.",rightAnswerIds:["a"],answers:{a:"corrected",b:"are corrected",c:"were corrected",d:"were being corrected"}}]},{header:{text:"Put the correct form of Passive Voice"},global:{fill:{normalize:{ignorePunctmarks:!0}}},exercises:[{type:"fill",lines:[[{text:"The message"},{preFill:"send",rightAnswerRegex:["was sent","i"]},{text:"to the wrong recipient."}]]},{type:"fill",lines:[[{text:"The old building"},{preFill:"demolish",rightAnswerRegex:["is being demolished","i"]},{text:"to make way for a new skyscraper."}]]},{type:"fill",lines:[[{text:"Our favorite song"},{preFill:"play",rightAnswerRegex:["is being played","i"]},{text:"on the radio right now."}]]},{type:"fill",lines:[[{text:"The package"},{preFill:"deliver",rightAnswerRegex:["will be delivered","i"]},{text:"to your doorstep by noon."}]]},{type:"fill",lines:[[{text:"The artwork"},{preFill:"admire",rightAnswerRegex:["is being admired","i"]},{text:"by art enthusiasts at the gallery."}]]},{type:"fill",lines:[[{text:"The secret"},{preFill:"reveal",rightAnswerRegex:["was revealed","i"]},{text:"by mistake during the conversation."}]]},{type:"fill",lines:[[{text:"The movie"},{preFill:"watch",rightAnswerRegex:["was watched","i"]},{text:"by millions of people on its opening night."}]]},{type:"fill",lines:[[{text:"The lost keys"},{preFill:"find",rightAnswerRegex:["were found","i"]},{text:"in the backyard by my brother."}]]},{type:"fill",lines:[[{text:"The book"},{preFill:"read",rightAnswerRegex:["is being read","i"]},{text:"by the entire class for their assignment."}]]},{type:"fill",lines:[[{text:"The cookies"},{preFill:"eat",rightAnswerRegex:["were eaten","i"]},{text:"by the children while we were away."}]]}]},{header:{text:"Choose the correct option"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"The old building ____ to make way for a new one.",rightAnswerIds:["d"],answers:{a:"was demolishing",b:"is demolishing",c:"demolishes",d:"was demolished"}},{type:"test",question:"The cake ____ by my grandmother.",rightAnswerIds:["b"],answers:{a:"baked",b:"was baked",c:"bakes",d:"is baking"}},{type:"test",question:"The car ____ by John yesterday.",rightAnswerIds:["d"],answers:{a:"drove",b:"is driving",c:"drives",d:"was driven"}},{type:"test",question:"The keys ____ on the kitchen counter.",rightAnswerIds:["c"],answers:{a:"was left",b:"leaves",c:"were left",d:"leave"}},{type:"test",question:"The concert ____ at the stadium.",rightAnswerIds:["d"],answers:{a:"was holding",b:"holds",c:"is held",d:"was held"}},{type:"test",question:"The movie ____ in Hollywood.",rightAnswerIds:["d"],answers:{a:"films",b:"filmed",c:"was filming",d:"is filmed"}},{type:"test",question:"The tickets ____ by her.",rightAnswerIds:["d"],answers:{a:"bought",b:"are buying",c:"was buying",d:"were bought"}},{type:"test",question:"The new restaurant ____ last week.",rightAnswerIds:["d"],answers:{a:"is opened",b:"opened",c:"opens",d:"was opened"}},{type:"test",question:"The problem ____ by the team.",rightAnswerIds:["c"],answers:{a:"solves",b:"solved",c:"was solved",d:"is solving"}},{type:"test",question:"The mistakes ____ by him.",rightAnswerIds:["c"],answers:{a:"corrects",b:"corrected",c:"are corrected",d:"was correcting"}}]}]};export{e as default};
